Guide to the William Benton Papers 1839-1973
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Subseries 3: Business Career
    - Sub-subseries 4: Encyclopaedia Britannica
      - General, 1943 (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - General, 1944 (Box 229, Folder 4)
      - General, 1945 (Box 229, Folder 5)
      - General, 1946 (Box 229, Folder 6)
      - A-C, general (Box 229, Folder 7)
      - Arnspiger, Clyde (Box 229, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees, Special Committee on Encyclopaedia Britannica (Box 229, Folder 9)
      - Collections (Box 229, Folder 10)
      - Corey, Stephen M. (Box 229, Folder 11)
      - D-G, general (Box 230, Folder 1)
      - Daly, Rose H. (Box 230, Folder 2)
      - Debevoise, E. Whitney (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Disney, Walt (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Dunham, Franklin A. (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Eleff, G. I., 1943 (Box 230, Folder 6)
      - ERPI, 1932-1936 (Box 230, Folder 7)
      - ERPI, 1937-1939 (Box 230, Folder 8)
      - ERPI, general, #1 (Box 230, Folder 9)
      - ERPI, general, #2 (Box 230, Folder 10)
      - Fellowships (Box 230, Folder 11)
      - Gacesa, Katherine, 1946-1947 (Box 230, Folder 12)
      - General Education Board (Box 230, Folder 13)
      - Grubbs, Harry (Box 230, Folder 14)
      - H-L, general (Box 230, Folder 15)
      - Hansen, C.F., 1947 (Box 230, Folder 16)
      - M-P, general (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - McClintock, Miller (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - McGilvray, John (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - McGraw, James H., 1943-1946 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - McNeil, Hector, 1948-1951 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - McNeil, 1952 (Box 231, Folder 6)
      - McNeil, Jan.-Apr. 1953 (Box 231, Folder 7)
      - McNeil, May-Aug. 1953 (Box 231, Folder 8)
      - McNeil, Sept.-Dec. 1953 (Box 231, Folder 9)
      - McNeil, Jan.-Mar. 1954 (Box 231, Folder 10)
      - McNeil, Apr.-June 1954 (Box 231, Folder 11)
      - McNeil, July-Sept. 1954 (Box 231, Folder 12)
      - McNeil, Oct. 1954-1957 (Box 231, Folder 13)
      - Movies (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Negotiations, #1 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Negotiations, #2 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - Operating Committee (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - Powell, E. H., 1942-1943 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Powell, 1944 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - Powell, 1945 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Promotion, 1943-1944 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - R-T, general (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Schoenwald, Lou C., 1943 (Box 233, Folder 6)
      - Schoenwald, 1944-1945 (Box 233, Folder 7)
      - Schuster, Max L. (Box 233, Folder 8)
      - Stuber, A. (Box 233, Folder 9)
      - Tams, W. G. (Box 233, Folder 10)
      - Tompkins, Lionel (Box 233, Folder 11)
      - Wood, Robert E. (Box 233, Folder 12)
      - U-Z, general (Box 233, Folder 13)
      - Yust, Walter (Box 233, Folder 14)
      - A, general (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - B-Bi, general (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - Bo-Bz, general (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Brodshaug, Melvin (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Browne, Barbara (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - Brubaker, Robert (Box 234, Folder 6)
      - Ca-Ce, general (Box 234, Folder 7)
      - Ch-Cl, general (Box 234, Folder 8)
      - Co-Cz, general (Box 234, Folder 9)
      - Colmes, Walter (Box 234, Folder 10)
      - Corson, John J. (Box 234, Folder 11)
      - Cox, Paul (Box 234, Folder 12)
      - Da-De, general (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - Di-Dz, general (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Dolphin, A. E. and E. T. (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - E-F, general (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Economic Cooperation Administration (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Foster, Norman (Box 235, Folder 6)
      - Ga-Go, general (Box 235, Folder 7)
      - Gr-Gz, general (Box 235, Folder 8)
      - Great Books Foundation, 1949 (Box 235, Folder 9)
      - Ha, general (Box 235, Folder 10)
      - Hart, Lidbury and Associates (Box 235, Folder 11)
      - He-Hi, general (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - High, Stanley (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Ho-Hz, general (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - I-K, general (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Kapp, Edgar (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - L, general (Box 236, Folder 6)
      - Ma, general (Box 236, Folder 7)
      - Mc, general (Box 236, Folder 8)
      - Me-Mz, general (Box 236, Folder 9)
      - N-O, general (Box 236, Folder 10)
      - O'Brien, Dale (Box 236, Folder 11)
      - P-Q, general (Box 236, Folder 12)
      - Ra-Ri, general (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Ro-Rz, general (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Sa-Sc, general (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Se, general (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Sh-Si, general (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Sm-Ste, general (Box 237, Folder 6)
      - Sti-Sz, general (Box 237, Folder 7)
      - T, general (Box 237, Folder 8)
      - U-Wa, general (Box 237, Folder 9)
      - Waugh, George M. (Box 237, Folder 10)
      - We-Wh, general (Box 237, Folder 11)
      - Wi, general (Box 237, Folder 12)
      - Wo-Z, general (Box 237, Folder 13)
      - Wygant, Foster, #1 (Box 237, Folder 14)
      - Wygant, #2 (Box 237, Folder 15)
      - A-C, general (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Allen, Lewis, 1960 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - American Cancer Society, 1964-1972 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Ankerman, Gerard J., 1962 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Armitage, John, 1958-1971 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Ba-Be, general (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - Bassow, Whitman, 1964-1968 (Box 238, Folder 7)
      - Bi-Bri, general (Box 238, Folder 8)
      - Brandt, Harry, 1958-1970 (Box 238, Folder 9)
      - Bro-Bu, general (Box 238, Folder 10)
      - Ca-Col, general (Box 238, Folder 11)
      - College of Advanced Science, 1958 (Box 238, Folder 12)
      - Conger, Dorothy and Robert, 1958-1970 (Box 238, Folder 13)
      - Cowan, Lester, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 14)
      - Craner, Lawrence, 1965-1966 (Box 238, Folder 15)
      - Curtis acquisition, pros and cons, 1959-1960 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Curtis acquisition, pros and cons, 1961 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Curtis acquisition, pros and cons, 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Curtis acquisition, pros and cons, 1963-1964 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Curtis acquisition, pros and cons, 1965 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Curtis acquisition, negotiations, 1959-1960 (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Curtis acquisition, negotiations, Jan.-Sept. 1961 (Box 239, Folder 7)
      - Curtis acquisition, negotiations, Oct.-Dec. 1961 (Box 239, Folder 8)
      - Curtis acquisition, negotiations, 1962 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Curtis acquisition, negotiations, 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Curtis acquisition, negotiations, 1965 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Curtis acquisition, Cecil King, 1965 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Curtis acquisition, corporate structure, 1958-1962 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Curtis acquisition, financial analysis, 1959-1960 (Box 240, Folder 6)
      - Curtis acquisition, financial analysis, 1961 (Box 240, Folder 7)
      - Curtis acquisition, financial analysis, 1962-1965 (Box 240, Folder 8)
      - Curtis acquisition, financing, 1960-1962 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Curtis acquisition, financing, Benton stock, 1960-1962 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Curtis acquisition, financing, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Curtis acquisition, Holiday Magazine, 1961-1965 (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Curtis acquisition, Saturday Evening Post, 1961-1965 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Curtis acquisition, Culligan, Matthew J., 1962-1971 (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - D, general (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - D'Alton, V., 1960-1961 (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - Davies, Ernest, 1960-1969 (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Dawson, Frank, 1961 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - Del Solar, Charlotte, 1969-1972 (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - D'Huc, Count, 1958 (Box 242, Folder 6)
      - Downs, James C., Jr., 1958-1969 (Box 242, Folder 7)
      - Doyle, John and Angela, 1958-1972 (Box 242, Folder 8)
      - Draper, Dorothy, 1961 (Box 242, Folder 9)
      - Dudley, C. W., 1968-1972 (Box 242, Folder 10)
      - Dumbrill, Richard, 1970 (Box 242, Folder 11)
      - E-F, general (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - English language and Britannica Institute, Jan.-Sept. 1966 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - English language and Britannica Institute, Oct.-Dec. 1966 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - English language and Britannica Institute, 1967 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - English language and Britannica Institute, 1969-1970 (Box 243, Folder 5)
      - English language and Britannica Institute, resources, 1969-1970 (Box 243, Folder 6)
      - Evans, Carol, 1958-1965 (Box 243, Folder 7)
      - Franklin Book Programs, Inc., 1967-1970 (Box 243, Folder 8)
      - G, general (Box 243, Folder 9)
      - Gassaway, F. Drennan, 1964 (Box 243, Folder 10)
      - Goldenson, Lenoard, 1962-1972 (Box 243, Folder 11)
      - Goldsen, Joseph M., 1961-1972 (Box 243, Folder 12)
      - Goodlad, John I., 1964-1969 (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Goodman, Lord, 1966-1968 (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - Granik, Theodore, 1958-1971 (Box 244, Folder 3)
      - Great Books Foundation, 1958-1968 (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - Guth, Oscar A., 1967-1971 (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - H, general (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - Haley, Sir William, 1967-1972 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - Harari, Robert, 1965 (Box 244, Folder 8)
      - Hiatt, Bert, 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 9)
      - Hiraizumi, Wataru, 1968-1970 (Box 244, Folder 10)
      - I-J, general (Box 244, Folder 11)
      - Johnson, T. Loftin, 1958 (Box 244, Folder 12)
      - Jolson, Marvin and Betty, 1968-1971 (Box 244, Folder 13)
      - Jones, Randolph, 1962 (Box 244, Folder 14)
      - Jones, William J., 1959-1962 (Box 244, Folder 15)
      - K, general (Box 244, Folder 16)
      - Keetch, John, 1958-1973 (Box 244, Folder 17)
      - L, general (Box 244, Folder 18)
      - Lubell, Samuel, 1958 (Box 244, Folder 19)
      - Ma-Mc, general (Box 245, Folder 1)
      - Macy, John W., Jr., 1969-1970 (Box 245, Folder 2)
      - Marin, Allan, 1961-1962 (Box 245, Folder 3)
      - Martin, David, 1968-1971 (Box 245, Folder 4)
      - McNeil, Sheila (Mrs. Hector) and Craig, 1958-1964 (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - McNeil, 1965-1972 (Box 245, Folder 6)
      - Me-Mz, general (Box 245, Folder 7)
      - Michaelis, Arnold, 1958-1968 (Box 245, Folder 8)
      - Miller, Edwin B., 1965-1966 (Box 245, Folder 9)
      - Morison, Stanley, 1960-1962 (Box 245, Folder 10)
      - Morison, 1963 (Box 245, Folder 11)
      - Morison, 1964-1965 (Box 245, Folder 12)
      - Morison, 1966-1967 (Box 245, Folder 13)
      - N-O, general (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - National Library Week, 1958-1961 (Box 246, Folder 2)
      - Nelson, David D., 1962-1968 (Box 246, Folder 3)
      - Nerber, John, 1958-1960 (Box 246, Folder 4)
      - P-Q, general (Box 246, Folder 5)
      - Plaut, Ed, 1958-1964 (Box 246, Folder 6)
      - Polk, Louis F., Jr., 1969-1972 (Box 246, Folder 7)
      - Preble, Robert C., Sr. and Jr., 1958-1971 (Box 246, Folder 8)
      - R, general (Box 246, Folder 9)
      - Rhodes, John and Irena, 1958-1962 (Box 246, Folder 10)
      - Rhodes, 1963-1964 (Box 246, Folder 11)
      - Rhodes, 1965-1966 (Box 247, Folder 1)
      - Rhodes, 1967-1969 (Box 247, Folder 2)
      - Rhodes, 1970-1973 (Box 247, Folder 3)
      - S, general, #1 (Box 247, Folder 4)
      - S, #2 (Box 247, Folder 5)
      - S, #3 (Box 247, Folder 6)
      - Semenko, Serge (Box 247, Folder 7)
      - Simon, Stanley (Box 247, Folder 8)
      - Stavrianos, L.S. (Box 247, Folder 9)
      - T, general (Box 247, Folder 10)
      - Theobald, Robert, 1962-1965 (Box 247, Folder 11)
      - Thompson, Paul, 1962-1973 (Box 247, Folder 12)
      - V, general (Box 247, Folder 13)
      - Wh-Wz, general (Box 247, Folder 14)
      - Wiser, Ralph E., II, 1961-1962 (Box 247, Folder 15)
      - X-Z, general (Box 247, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 4: Public Life
    - Sub-subseries 1: Public relations and project ideas, 1958-1973
      - Administration, general, 1961-1970 (Box 248, Folder 1)
      - Administration, general, 1971 (Box 248, Folder 2)
      - Administration, general, 1972 (Box 248, Folder 3)
      - Administration, general, 1973 (Box 248, Folder 4)
      - Administration, consultants, Christman, Henry, 1960-1962 (Box 248, Folder 5)
      - Administration, consultants, Hyman, Sidney, 1961-1966 (Box 248, Folder 6)
      - Administration, consultants, Josephs, Ray, 1961-1962 (Box 248, Folder 7)
      - Administration, consultants, Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1959-1962 (Box 248, Folder 8)
      - Administration, consultants, Trace, Arthur S., Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 248, Folder 9)
      - Administration, consultants, Urrows, Henry, 1961-1964 (Box 249, Folder 1)
      - Administration, consultants, Wilson, William, 1959-1961 (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - General projects, 1958-1961 (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - General projects, 1962 (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - General projects, 1963-1964 (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - General projects, 1965-1966 (Box 249, Folder 6)
      - Benton firsts, 1955-1964 (Box 249, Folder 7)
      - Biography project, 1961-1965 (Box 249, Folder 8)
      - Business and economics projects, general, 1959-1969 (Box 249, Folder 9)
      - Business and economics projects, image, 1959-1962 (Box 249, Folder 10)
      - Business and economics projects, boards of directors, 1959 (Box 249, Folder 11)
      - Business and economics projects, entrepreneurship, 1964 (Box 249, Folder 12)
      - Business and economics projects, selling, 1959-1963 (Box 249, Folder 13)
      - Communications projects, general, 1949-1967 (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Communications projects, United Nations Conference on Freedom of Information (Geneva Conference), 1947-1948 (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - Communications projects, United Nations Conference on Freedom of Information (Geneva Conference), 1948 (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Communications projects, United Nations Conference on Freedom of Information (Geneva Conference), 1951-1953 (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Communications projects, Information Program, 1955-1963 (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - Communications projects, Information Program, 1965-1969 (Box 250, Folder 6)
      - Communications projects, Smith-Mundt Act, 1958-1961 (Box 250, Folder 7)
      - Communications projects, mass media, 1959-1962 (Box 250, Folder 8)
      - Communications projects, Voice of America, 1957-1962 (Box 250, Folder 9)
      - Education projects, general, 1958-1965 (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - Education projects, image, "William Benton, Educationist" (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Education projects, image, 1957-1962 (Box 251, Folder 3)
      - Education projects, image, 1963-1969 (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - Education projects, Benton's book (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - Education projects, honorary degrees (Box 251, Folder 6)
      - Education projects, liberal arts, 1954-1960 (Box 251, Folder 7)
      - Latin America, 1960-1961 (Box 251, Folder 8)
      - McCarthy project, 1959-1973 (Box 251, Folder 9)
      - Politics and government projects, general, 1958-1964 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - Politics and government projects, general, 1965-1970 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - Politics and government projects, image, 1959-1964 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - Politics and government projects, America First Committee, 1964 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Politics and government projects, Campaign, 1964 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Politics and government projects, Democratic administration appointments, 1960-1961 (Box 252, Folder 6)
      - Politics and government projects, Democratic administration appointments, 1962-1967 (Box 252, Folder 7)
      - Politics and government projects, presidential elections, 1960-1961 (Box 252, Folder 8)
      - Politics and government projects, presidential elections, Schlesinger book, 1960 (Box 252, Folder 9)
      - Politics and government projects, campaign practices reforms, 1950-1959 (Box 252, Folder 10)
      - Politics and government projects, campaign practices reforms, 1960-1970 (Box 252, Folder 11)
      - Politics and government projects, reforms, 1958-1962 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Politics and government projects, reforms, 1963-1968 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Politics and government projects, reforms, federal salary system, 1963 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Radio and TV interviews, 1960-1964 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Soviet challenge, 1958-1962 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Soviet challenge, 1963-1966 (Box 253, Folder 6)
      - General image, 1959-1967 (Box 253, Folder 7)
    - Sub-subseries 2: America First, 1939-1942
      - Advertisements, 1941 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Bliss, Robert L., 1940-1941 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Borgese, G. A., May 1939-Feb. 1940 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Borgese, Mar.-June 1940 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Borgese, Aug.-Nov. 1940 (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Bowles, Chester, Dec. 1940-July 1941 (Box 254, Folder 6)
      - "Copperhead" advertisement, 1941 (Box 254, Folder 7)
      - General files, Nov. 1940-Jan. 1941 (Box 254, Folder 8)
      - General files, Feb. 1941-Mar. 1941 (Box 254, Folder 9)
      - General files, Apr. 1941-May 1941 (Box 254, Folder 10)
      - General files, July 1941-Dec. 1941 (Box 254, Folder 11)
      - Hutchins/Samuel E. Gill poll, 1941 (Box 254, Folder 12)
      - LaFollette, Robert and Philip, 1940-1941 (Box 254, Folder 13)
      - Charles A. Lindbergh speeches, 1941 (Box 254, Folder 14)
      - Stuart, R. Douglas, Jr., Oct. 1940-Apr. 1941 (Box 254, Folder 15)
      - Stuart, May 1941 (Box 254, Folder 16)
      - Stuart, June 1941-Jan. 1942 (Box 254, Folder 17)
      - University of Chicago Round Table, May 1941 (Box 254, Folder 18)
      - Wood, Gen. Robert E., Jan. 1941-Jan. 1942 (Box 254, Folder 19)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Committee for Economic Development
      - General correspondence, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - General correspondence, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - General correspondence, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - General correspondence, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - General correspondence, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - A-C, general, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 6)
      - A-C, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 7)
      - A-C, 1941-1957 (Box 255, Folder 8)
      - Auditor (Box 255, Folder 9)
      - Benton, William (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Board of Trustees (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Brady, Robert (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - By-laws (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Calkins, Robert (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - D-G, general, #1 (Box 256, Folder 6)
      - D-G, #2 (Box 256, Folder 7)
      - D-G, #3 (Box 256, Folder 8)
      - Dodd, Norman (Box 256, Folder 9)
      - Dooley, Edwin B. (Box 256, Folder 10)
      - Field development: divisional chart, 1945 (Box 256, Folder 11)
      - Financial statements, 1942-1944 (Box 256, Folder 12)
      - Flanders, Ralph, 1942-1945 (Box 256, Folder 13)
      - Fletcher, C. Scott, 1944-1945 (Box 256, Folder 14)
      - Folsom, Marion B., 1942-1943 (Box 256, Folder 15)
      - Fortune article, 1942-1943 (Box 256, Folder 16)
      - Francis, Clarence, 1942-1945 (Box 256, Folder 17)
      - Gager, Curt (Box 256, Folder 18)
      - Grant, Will C., 1943 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - H-L, general, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - H-L, 1944-1945 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Hoffman, Paul G., 1942-1945 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Hormel, Jay C., 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Hyde, Anthony, 1944-1945 (Box 257, Folder 6)
      - I-L, general, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 7)
      - Inter-American Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 8)
      - Jacoby, Neil, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 9)
      - Johnson, Henry, 1944-1945 (Box 257, Folder 10)
      - Lasswell, Harold D., 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 11)
      - M-P, general, #1 (Box 257, Folder 12)
      - M-P, #2 (Box 257, Folder 13)
      - M-P, #3 (Box 257, Folder 14)
      - Meetings (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - R, general (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Regional chairmen (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Research Advisory Board (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Research Committee, #1 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Research Committee, #2 (Box 258, Folder 6)
      - Riis, Roger William (Box 258, Folder 7)
      - Ruml, Beardsley (Box 258, Folder 8)
      - S, general, #1 (Box 258, Folder 9)
      - S, #2 (Box 258, Folder 10)
      - Scherman, Harry, 1942-1943 (Box 258, Folder 11)
      - Schleiter, Walter B., 1943 (Box 258, Folder 12)
      - Slichter, Sumner, 1942-1943 (Box 258, Folder 13)
      - Stauffer, Grant (Box 258, Folder 14)
      - T, general (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Test cities, 1942 (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - U-W, general (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Y-Z, general (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - General correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - General correspondence, 1953 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - General correspondence, 1954 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - General correspondence, 1955 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - General correspondence, 1956 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - General correspondence, 1957 (Box 260, Folder 6)
      - Ralph Flanders bill (Box 260, Folder 7)
      - J-L, general (Box 260, Folder 8)
      - M-R, general (Box 260, Folder 9)
      - Myers, Howard (Box 260, Folder 10)
      - S, general (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - T-Z, general (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Thomson, J. Cameron (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - White, Nate (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Wilde, Frazar B. (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Williams, Walter (Box 261, Folder 6)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1958 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1959 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1960-1961 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1962 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 262, Folder 6)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 262, Folder 7)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1969 (Box 262, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 262, Folder 9)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1972 (Box 263, Folder 1)
      - Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 263, Folder 2)
      - Reports, 1961 (Box 263, Folder 3)
      - Reports, Jan.-June 1962 (Box 263, Folder 4)
      - Reports, July-Dec. 1962 (Box 263, Folder 5)
      - Reports, 1963 (Box 263, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1964 (Box 264, Folder 1)
      - Reports, 1966 (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Reports, 1967 (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 1970 (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - Reports, 1971 (Box 264, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1972 (Box 264, Folder 7)
      - Reports, The Economic and Social Impact of the New Broadcast Media, 1971-1972 (Box 264, Folder 8)
      - Research and Policy Committee and Advisory Board, 1958-1960 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Politics
      - Sub-sub-subseries 1: 1948-1957
        - Acheson, Dean, 1948-1950 (Box 265, Folder 1)
        - Acheson, 1951 (Box 265, Folder 2)
        - Acheson, 1952-1957 (Box 265, Folder 3)
        - Anderson, Clinton P., 1948-1957 (Box 265, Folder 4)
        - Arpaia, Anthony, 1950-1957 (Box 265, Folder 5)
        - Ba-Bl, general (Box 265, Folder 6)
        - Bailey, John M., 1949 (Box 266, Folder 1)
        - Bailey, Jan.-June 1950 (Box 266, Folder 2)
        - Bailey, July-Dec. 1950 (Box 266, Folder 3)
        - Bailey, Jan.-June 1951 (Box 266, Folder 4)
        - Bailey, July-Dec. 1951 (Box 266, Folder 5)
        - Bailey, 1952 (Box 266, Folder 6)
        - Bailey, 1953 (Box 266, Folder 7)
        - Bailey, 1954-1955 (Box 266, Folder 8)
        - Bailey, 1956-1957 (Box 266, Folder 9)
        - Bailey, Stephen K., 1951-1957 (Box 267, Folder 1)
        - Barkley, Alben W., 1948-1955 (Box 267, Folder 2)
        - Barrett, Edward W., 1948-1949 (Box 267, Folder 3)
        - Barrett, Jan.-June 1950 (Box 267, Folder 4)
        - Barrett, July-Dec. 1950 (Box 267, Folder 5)
        - Barrett, Jan.-May 1951 (Box 267, Folder 6)
        - Barrett, June-Dec. 1951 (Box 267, Folder 7)
        - Barrett, 1952-1956 (Box 267, Folder 8)